{
    "id": "af75004b789e48029f8b9aa73201a484",
    "title": "Coordinating Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They were poor, ………………. often suffered great hardship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "de15f235953f42bd853fa1066d6847c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He overslept himself …………………. thus missed the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e8df446768b447c49ccbd38e1c682b3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "That coat cannot be mine, ……………… it is too big for me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fe483375ba614ec88f013d161a30bb5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "As a boy he had never been to school, and ………………….. he had no opportunity of learning to read and write.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "therefore",
                "for",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8ade26df16c74711bd99aeaa6f645494"
        },
        {
            "question": "This must not happen again, ……………… you will be dismissed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "but",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3524fb2d5c6c4fcbb929bf78eb695d32"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is rich, ………………. he is not happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "therefore",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "42b8bbe3152946d7a26a3fc7a130682b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hurry up, ……………….. you will be late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "or",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d8af216ca54345e6b69f41873d79a79f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He must have done his duty, ……………….. he is a conscientious man.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "so",
                "therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b344dbd17e54adda7503b36a041b92f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He tried hard, ………………. he did not succeed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "and",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c5a4464c8f914c9fab667866b9a24416"
        },
        {
            "question": "The parents were horrified ………………. they saw blood stains on the floor and no sign of their child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "therefore",
                "for",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e5fc6d8d027947e5a5e0bdc324fc4929"
        }
    ]
}